// Answer text must be under 25 characters otherwise they'll be truncated
// Answer value but be the lowercase LETTER of the correct answer (a, b, c, or d)
// All games must be 10 questions - do not delete any!

module.exports = {
  gameType: 'text',
  questions: [
    {
      question: '"Tool Time" was a show within what other show?', 
      a: 'This Olde House', 
      b: 'This Old House',
      c: 'All That',
      d: 'Home Improvement',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'Where is the Sea of Tranquility located?', 
      a: 'Spain', 
      b: 'Saudi Arabia',
      c: 'Israel',
      d: 'The Moon',
      answer: 'd'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the most common letter in the English alphabet?', 
      a: 'E', 
      b: 'S',
      c: 'A',
      d: 'I',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What does a Scoville unit measure?', 
      a: 'Molecular mass', 
      b: 'Spiciness',
      c: 'Computer mouse movement',
      d: 'How fast a beard grows',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What company makes the Butterfinger bar?', 
      a: 'Mars', 
      b: 'Nestle',
      c: 'Hershey',
      d: 'Lindt',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'What does "NC" mean in an NC-17 movie rating?', 
      a: 'Nudity-Crudeness', 
      b: 'Nude Content',
      c: 'No Children',
      d: 'Not Compliant',
      answer: 'c'
    },
    {
      question: 'Where did rap superstar Eminem grow up?', 
      a: 'Chicago', 
      b: 'Detroit',
      c: 'NYC',
      d: 'Oklahoma',
      answer: 'b'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which actor was NOT a regular on "Whose Line Is it Anyway"?', 
      a: 'Ricky Gervais', 
      b: 'Ryan Stiles',
      c: 'Colin Mochrie',
      d: 'Wayne Brady',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the main ingredient in a falafel?', 
      a: 'Chickpea', 
      b: 'Flour',
      c: 'Pita',
      d: 'Bulgur Wheat',
      answer: 'a'
    },
    {
      question: 'Where is the uvula located?', 
      a: 'Next to the Cerebellum', 
      b: 'Female genitals',
      c: 'Throat',
      d: 'Male genitals',
      answer: 'c'
    }
  ]
};